翻译: 钟钟 longli 小清欣
兄弟 来接我和Amy的车2分钟内就到了
Ok, duke, car's picking me and Amy up in two minutes.
你确定能在我坐游轮的时候帮我跟着点我的案子
You sure you're cool keeping tabs on my cases while I'm on the cruise?
校对: FENGYUDEER
当然了 你要玩得开心哦
You bet. I hope you have a great time.
嘿 但是别交新的好朋友
Hey, don't make any new best friends.
后期: 尘世劫
哦 也许你就不该去
Oh. Maybe you shouldn't go.
开玩笑吗 我想去这个一周游轮行都想疯了
Are you kidding? I am psyched to go on this week-long cruise,
压制: 怪查理
就坐在那无所事事
just sitting around doing nothing.
过着懒洋洋的惬意生活咯
Straight up living that slug life, y'all.
新鲜出炉的游轮活动项目哦
Cruise itineraries, hot out of the laminator.
谁准备好享受毫不停歇安排满满的欢乐时光了
Who's ready for some nonstop totally scheduled fun?
哦 我其实想的我们就 坐在水边
Oh, I actually thought we could just...sit by the pool,
吃着无限量的虾 看看身体能有什么变化
eat unlimited shrimp, and see what it does to our bodies.
想得不错
That's cute.
只是不知道时间够不够
I don't know if there's gonna be time, though.
这次航游提供77种活动
The cruise offers 77 activities,
我给我们俩报名参加了76个
and I signed us up for 76 of them.
因为那个寡妇速配相亲好像蛮晦气的
Speed dating for widows seemed like a bummer.
好吧 对这次游轮旅行有一点点
Okay, so slightly different perspectives
不同看法哦
going into this cruise.
这就叫惬意生活话题
Call it the slug life talking,
而且我觉得这事船到桥头自然直
but I think it's gonna work itself out.
再见咯 同事们
Good-bye, coworkers,
或者像在海上说话那样
or as they like to say at sea...
神烦警探
第三季 第十三集
电波诚译
- 这太棒了  - 是呀
- This is so great. - Yeah.
海鸥 有了
Seagulls, check.
大海 有了
The ocean, check.
一群穿超短裤的老年人
A gang of oldies in short shorts,
都在这儿了
check, check, check.
我们绝对在游轮上了
We are definitely on a cruise.
欢迎登船
Welcome aboard.
说"我爱旋转木马国际游轮有限责任公司"
Say, "I love Carousel Cruises International Ltd."
- 我爱旋转木马国际游轮有限公司  - 我可不想说
- I love Carousel Cruises International Ltd.  - I don't want to say that.
好了
All right.
远航派对在1小时后
So...the Sail Away party is in an hour,
在那之前 我安排了咱们去全龄钢琴酒吧
and until then, I have us scheduled to take in live music
听现场音乐会
at the all-ages piano lounge.
好吧好吧 或者我们可以直接去房间
Okay, okay. Or we could just head straight to the room.
我带了塑料布所以我们可以在床上吃虾了
I brought a plastic tarp so we can eat shrimp in bed.
但是全龄钢琴酒吧有无限量供应的玛格丽特哟
But the all-ages piano lounge has bottomless margaritas.
嗯
Eh.
也有加了土豆皮的饮料哦
They also have a drink with a potato skin in it.
哦 那就去这个全龄钢琴酒吧吧 尊敬的女士
Ohh. To the all-ages piano lounge, merlady.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
欢迎登船 女士们先生们
Welcome aboard, ladies and gentlemen,
特别是女士们
but especially ladies.
我熟悉这个声音
I know that voice.
准备好 现在是淫荡小黄曲时间
Get ready. It's time for some smush songs.
Doug Judy 庞蒂亚克大盗
Doug Judy. The Pontiac Bandit.
他就在这
He's here.
有关于暧昧的歌
We got songs about smushing,
也有卿卿我我时听的歌
songs for smushing to,
还有给小孩子的歌
songs for the kids.
这就是全龄钢琴音乐酒吧
This is the all-ages piano lounge.
不敢相信他就在这 我追查了他好几年
I can't believe he's here. I've been hunting him for years,
现在命运把他送到我脚边了
and now fate has dropped him right into my lap.
他看见我肯定会很惊讶
He's gonna be so surprised when he sees me.
嗨 Peralta 你来啦
Hey, Peralta, you made it.
怎么那么久才来 兄弟
What took you so long, brother?
好吧 看来他掩饰得挺好
Okay, seems like he's playing it pretty cool.
内心肯定惊慌失措
Probably more surprised on the inside.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
99分局
上午11:42
长官 Gina和我都很担心你
Sir, Gina and I are worried about you.
你都在喝第二罐苏打水了
You're drinking a second can of seltzer.
我需要它安抚我的紧张情绪
I need this to settle my nerves.
飓风Debbie就要来了
Hurricane Debbie is approaching.
我的妹妹Debbie 是个小题大做一惊一乍的女人
My little sister Debbie, she's a real drama queen.
Holt家一惊一乍的女人
The drama queen of the Holt family?
怎么 她是有一次笑得大声了吗
What, did she laugh out loud one time?
她大声笑了太多次了
She's laughed out loud multiple times.
长官 你定义一惊一乍的标准很低
Sir, you have a pretty low bar for what you consider drama.
有一次我在邮件里用了感叹号
Once, I used an exclamation point in a email.
Diana Ross 美国著名黑人女歌手
你就叫我Diana Ross
You called me Diana Ross.
我向你保证 在这件事上 我没有夸张
I assure you, in this case, I do not exaggerate.
Raymond
Raymond!
来了
Here.
你们自己判断吧
Judge for yourselves.
你在这呢
Here you are.
太好了 我的天啊
Great. Oh, my God.
我从火车站到这的路上
My trip here from the train station--
我保证我绝对听到出租车司机
hey, I swear to you I heard the cab driver
在嘀嘀咕咕"你今晚会死"
mumble under his breath, "You will die tonight."
这难道不是你听到的最疯狂的事吗
Is that not the most insane thing you have ever heard?
你能想象吗 Raymond
I mean, can you even, Raymond?
我简直 不能
I cannot...even.
死亡调查
下午1:36
我一段时间没看见她了
I hadn't seen her in a while.
她一个人住
She lived alone.
已经89岁高龄
She was 89 years old.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
没有强行入室痕迹和明显创伤
There's no forced entry or visible trauma.
很大可能是自然死亡
It's probably natural causes.
- 我们会四处看看  - 当然
- We'll take a look around. - Sure.
这个公寓真大
This huge apartment.
这有多大 是不是有1800平方英尺
What is this, like, 1,800 square feet?
裸露砖墙
Exposed brick.
有极好的自然采光
Got tons of natural light.
奇怪 我以为你会对煤气灶更感兴趣
Weird. I thought you'd be most exciting about the gas range.
这还有煤气灶
They have a gas range.
我一定要申请这套公寓
I have to apply for this apartment.
你看 这刚刚空出来
I mean, it just became available.
只有我们俩看见过
We're the only two people to see it.
这是你在纽约房产界
This is an opportunity you just don't get
千年难遇的机会啊
in New York real estate ever.
一位女士刚刚在这死去
A woman just died here.
别这么庸俗无礼
Don't be gross and disrespectful.
我了个去 快看这个衣帽间
Holy crap, look at all this closet space.
我也要申请
I'm applying too.
什么 你根本不需要衣帽间
What? You don't need closet space.
你大概只有 一件外套
You have, like, one outfit.
- 就让给我吧  - 不行
- Just let me have this. - No.
我们同时看见的
We saw it at the same time.
那就最强者赢
May the best man win.
游戏开始
Game on.
咳咳
Eh-hem
我是说 联系下一位死者亲属的游戏
I mean, the game of contacting the next of kin.
我就喜欢玩这种游戏
That's the game I like to play.
Peralta 你在这艘船上可不是巧合
Peralta, it's no coincidence you're on a ship.
你没参加任何比赛就得到免费游轮票
You won a free cruise without entering a contest.
你觉得这是怎么回事儿
How do you think that happened?
我不知道
I don't know.
Speed 2 电影<生死时速2> 故事背景设定在豪华邮轮上
也许是我买了<生死时速2>来看
Maybe it's because I bought "Speed 2" On DVD,
所以互联网认定游轮
and the Internet realized that cruises
是我的爱好之一
were one of my interests.
好电影 Sandy穿着纱裙
Great film. Sandy B. in a sarong.
太对了
Damn straight.
但是这个票是我给的
But the tix are all me.
我把你叫来是因为我有危险了
I brought you here 'cause I'm in peril.
切 危险
Pfft. Peril.
不许"切"我的危险
Don't "Pfft" My peril.
切
Pfft.
有人要杀我 我需要保护
Somebody's trying to kill me, and I need protection,
所以我叫来了我最好的朋友
so I sent for my best friend.
我不是你最好的朋友
I am not your best friend.
我是你最大的敌人 你好好记住了
I'm your worst enemy. Get that through your head.
就是这样的小打小闹
It's this kind of bickering
让我们成为这么可爱的一对
that makes us such an adorable couple.
管你怎么说 Judy 你被捕了
Whatever, Judy. You're under arrest.
你不能逮捕我 兄弟 我们在公海上呢
You can't arrest me, boo. We're in international waters,
同样我想抽多少大麻就抽多少
which is also why I can smoke as much weed as I want.
欢迎来到嗨爽之海哦
Welcome to the high seas.
不 这不可能是真的
No, no way that that's true.
Amy 告诉我我现在就能逮捕他
Amy, tell me I can arrest him right now.
Judy是对的 我们无权逮捕他
Judy's right. We have no jurisdiction.
严格来说这艘船现在在乌兹别克斯坦管辖范围内
Technically this boat flies under the flag of Uzbekistan.
哦噢 你的姑娘很了解乌兹别克斯坦哟
Uh-oh. Your girl knows about the Uzbeks. Oh.
但是船长能逮捕他
But the captain can have him arrested.
他在这艘船上完全有这个权力
He has total authority on this boat.
太好了 船长都爱我的
Perfect. Captains love me.
你就等着他或者她发现
Just wait until he or she
他们雇佣了一个罪犯吧
finds out they're employing a criminal.
嗯 差不多百分之四十的船员都是罪犯
Yeah, about 40% of the crew are criminals.
很难找到想在船上生活的正常人
It's hard to find normal people who want to live on a boat.
我自己就是逃税者
I, myself, am a tax evader.
我只需要在我们回到纽约前把他锁起来
I just need him locked up till we get back to New York.
你就不能把他关在船上的监狱里吗
Can't you just throw him in boat jail?
那叫船上禁闭室
It's called the brig.
他是我最棒的酒吧歌手
He is my best lounge singer,
而且我得让乘客分心
and I need to keep people distracted.
就我们之间说说 我们快没田园沙拉酱了
Just between us, we're nearly out of ranch dressing.
才第一天
On day one?
这些人简直就是动物
These people are animals.
听着 只要他在我船上
Listen, as long as he's on my boat,
Doug Judy就是自由的
Doug Judy is a free man.
Jack Amy 欢迎到我的船舱
Jake, Amy, welcome to my cabin,
也叫做 砰砰豪华舱
AKA the Boom-Boom Stateroom.
哇
Wow
这是皇室套房呀
This is a royale level suite.
没想到我还能亲眼见到
I never thought we'd see one in person.
这是给旋转木马游轮年度艺人
Little perk of being
小小的特殊待遇
Carousel Cruises' entertainer of the year.
那个人就是我哦 姑娘
Which I am, girrr-rl
唱走调了
A little pitch-y.
欢迎你们在这放松
You're welcome to chill here.
为了感谢你们保护我 这是我能做的最起码的事了
It's the least I can do to thank you for protecting me.
绝不可能 这个保护骗局本身就是骗局
Never. This protection scam is a scam.
你真的以为就因为你之前
Do you honestly think you can fool me again
成功骗过我无数次了 就又能骗我一次吗
just because you've successfully done it numerous times before?
听着 我以前的老大想让我死
Look, my old boss wants me dead.
所以我在这艘船上隐姓埋名
I've been laying low on this ship,
但是我从一个内部朋友那得到消息
and I got word from a friend on the inside
他们已经找到我了 派了杀手
that they found me, and there's a hitman
要来结束我宝贵的生命
coming to end my beautiful life.
所以我才会寄给你免费船票
That's why I sent you the free tickets.
不 不 不可能 我不会信的
No! No, no way. I'm not buying it.
你再也不能从我这逃走
You can't get away from me again.
Amy和我在这次浪漫航行中的每一分每一秒
Amy and I are gonna spend every second of our romantic cruise
都会盯紧你 可以吧
watching you, assuming that's okay?
对 我们会这样做
Yep. That's what we're gonna do.
耶
Yeah.
我只能把这个活动计划丢一边了
I'll just get rid of this itinerary.
别别别 Amy 不要丢这个
No, no, no, no, Ames, don't put that down.
我们得在这个杀手找到我前找到他
We have to find the hitman before he finds me.
我想这个东西能带我们去船上每一个角落
I'm guessing this'll take us all over the boat.
哦耶 这是角缝情况
Oh, yeah, that's an ENAC sitch right there.
"每个角落和缝隙"
"Every Nook And Cranny."
完美 我们会把这个坏人找遍每个角缝
Perfect. We'll just ENAC sitch, uh, of this bitch.
99分局
上午11:42
你妹妹怎么样了 长官
How's it going with your sister, sir?
昨晚她告诉我很多
Well, last night, she told me in a great detail
关于她和她教练一场争吵的细节
about a fight she got into with her trainer,
她说这个人偷了她的梳子
whom she accused of stealing a hairbrush.
现在她正在电话里对着老妈大吼大叫
Now she's on the phone, screaming at our mother.
我们会把她支开的
We'll keep her out of your hair.
我对转移人注意力很在行
I'm good at distracting people.
我每天都和孩子们这样
It's what I do with my toddlers all day long.
她对气球做的小动物感觉怎么样
How does she feel about balloon animals?
我确定她和它们有种复杂的关系
I'm sure she has a complicated relationship with them.
- Ray  - 她来了
- Ray! - Here she comes.
不要气球做的小动物
No balloon animals.
你绝对不信老妈是怎么想的
You ain't gonna believe mom's take on this.
她觉得我应该道歉
She thinks I'm the one who should apologize
就因为最后梳子是在我车上
just 'cause it turns out the hairbrush ended up being in my car.
我很乐意再讨论几次你梳子的事
Yes, I'd love to discuss your hairbrush for even more time,
但是我有些紧急的事情要处理
but I have some pressing police matters to attend to.
看看你 大忙人
Look at you. Always working.
我那个幽默的大哥哥去哪了
What happened to my fun big brother?
幽默 我向来不幽默 把这话收回去
Fun? I was never fun. You take that back.
我想她不是这个意思
I'm sure she didn't mean anything by it, sir.
在还小的时候 我们会跑去地下室
When we were little, we would go down in the basement,
然后他会给我们盖堡垒
and he would build us a fort.
我们一待就是一整天
We would stay down there all day.
Ray会唱那些蠢蠢的自编歌曲
And Ray would sing these silly little made-up songs.
美国著名作曲家
Gershwin兄弟的歌可不是什么蠢蠢的瞎编的歌
George and Ira Gershwin did not compose silly, made-up songs.
呃Debbie 我带你在纽约转转吧
Uh, Debbie, let me show you New York, okay?
建筑啊 地铁啊 银行啊
The buildings, the subway, the bank,
烘干机啊 我有事要去跑跑腿
the dry cleaner-- I got to run some errands.
好主意 Gina
Oh, that's a great idea, Gina.
Debbie 抱歉我没机会
Debbie, I'm so sorry I won't get a chance
在你来的时候多见见你
to see you much on your visit.
没什么大不了的
Uh, no thing but a chicken wing,
因为我要在这待六周
'cause I'm gonna be here for six weeks.
我要全身心地融入你的生活
I'ma be all up in your life, okay?
我做完五个了
I got five down.
我找到主题了 是船
I figured out the theme. It's boats.
好我明白了
Okay, I get it.
她是聪明惹人爱 你是爆脾气惹人爱
She's smart and lovable; you're scrappy and lovable;
你们两个一起闪闪惹人爱
together you're just lovable and lovable.
这个杀手在哪 Judy
Okay, so where's this hitman, Judy?
我不知道他们派谁来了
Look, I don't know who they sent,
但他在船上
but he's on the boat.
快看这个旅客名单
Check out this manifest.
有个叫Henry Coles的人在圣胡安登船
Somebody boarded in San Juan named Henry Coles.
Henry街和Coles街
Henry Street and Coles Street,
那是你布鲁克林旧赃车行街角的两条街
that's the corner of your old chop shop in Brooklyn.
- 这是个化名  - 嗯哼
- This is an alias. - Mm-hmm.
我的侍者哥儿们看了Henry Coles的客舱
And my porter buddy checked out Henry Coles' cabin,
他还没住进去
He hasn't been in it yet.
他躲在这条船的某个地方
He's hiding somewhere on this boat
时刻准备着出来杀我
ready to jump out and kill me at any moment.
很有可能就躲在我衣橱里
Probably creepin' around in my closet.
- 或者藏匿在救生艇里  - 或者躲在墙里
- Or stowed away in a lifeboat. - Or hiding in a wall.
或者龟缩在轮机室
Or holed up in the engine room.
隐蔽在灌木丛中
Camouflaged in the shrubbery.
美国<铁血战士>系列电影
掠夺者风格
Predator style.
不 我们不是在玩
No. We are not having fun.
我不会被你的诡计所迷惑
You will not suck me in with your wily charms.
Gotaro先生 你的咖啡 加奶 没放糖
Senor Gotaro, un cafe con leche, sin azucar.
谢谢
Gracias.
嗨 Gotaro先生 见到你很高兴
Hola, Mr. Gotaro. Good to see you.
我能和Rosa说句话吗
Can I talk to Rosa for a quick sec
是超级严肃的工作的事情
about some super serious police work?
我知道你要干什么
I know what you're trying to do.
你把他搞来是为了巴结他
You brought him in here to butter him up.
是 我已经做得
Yeah, and I've been laying it on...
很夸张了
real thick.
薄荷糖
Mint?
但是你犯了个天大的错误
Okay, but you're making a big mistake.
没人比Boyle还能跪舔巴结人
Nobody sucks up like a Boyle.
当然 你早就知道这个了因为你是聪明人
Of course, you knew that already because you're so smart.
我刚对你使了这招
I just did it to you.
好吧 小矮人
Fine, little man.
- 上吧  - 好
- Bring it. - Okay.
看起来你和我
Looks like you and I
要来一场愉快的老派跪舔了
are in a good, old-fashioned suck-off.
别叫它跪舔好吗
Don't call it a suck-off.
为什么不
Why not? Why shouldn't--
噢对对对对对
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是 嗯哼 对 明智 好
Totally, yep. Mm-hmm. Right. Smart. Good.
你自带了沙狐球的杆子
You brought your own shuffleboard stick?
tang也有阴道的意思
- 嗯哼  - 这叫做"球棍"
- Mm-hmm. - They're called tangs.
你应该高兴她有自己的球棍
You should be glad she has her own.
你可不想她用别的男人的"球棍"
You don't want her messing with another man's tang.
它们不可能叫球棍吧
There is no way they're called tangs.
真的是这样
It's true. They are.
biscuits有臀部的意思
沙狐球的盘子叫做"饼干"
And the disks are called biscuits.
- 是的  - "球棍"和"饼干"
- Yes. - Tangs and biscuits?
无言以对
That is so dumb.
我正式爱上了沙狐球
I officially love shuffleboard.
让出条路 我要抽打我的"饼干"了
Clear a path! I'm about to whip my biscuit!
呀
Yah!
Jake 你开心的时候
About time you smiled, Jake.
真的是在强颜欢笑啊
You've been a real tang in the mud.
- 好吧  - 嘿小建议
- All right. - Hey, little advice.
Amy很棒
Amy is great.
你想和她好下去
You want to keep her,
就要接纳她的爱好
be more receptive to her interests.
现在你扯太远了 Judy
All right, now you're taking it too far, Judy.
我不需要罪犯死对头的感情建议
I don't need relationship advice from my criminal archnemesis.
我只是想看到你们两个幸福
Look, I just want to see you two happy.
不 这只是你的另一条谎言
No. This is just another one of your lies,
就和那个杀手的谎言一样
just like your fake hitman.
这条船上有一个职业杀手
There is a hitman on this boat.
Henry Coles要来杀我
Henry Coles is coming to kill me.
不好意思
Excuse me?
- 什么  - 你刚叫我名字了
- What? - You said my name.
我是Henry Coles
I'm Henry Coles.
你是Henry Coles
You're Henry Coles?
我的医疗腕带上写着呢
According to my medical alert bracelet.
真有意思
Well, this is interesting.
这是Henry Coles 让我瞧瞧这个
This is Henry Coles. Let's just take a look at that.
上面写着 "Doug Judy是骗子"
Oh, it says, "Doug Judy is a liar."
其实上面写的是 我有跌倒的风险
Actually, it says I'm a fall risk.
好吧 你毁了我的梗 Henry
Okay, you're kind of ruining my burn here, Henry.
我就知道
I knew it.
我就知道Henry Coles是个
I knew Henry Coles was a 90-year old man
有一型糖尿病和肺气肿的90岁老头
with type 1 diabetes and emphysema.
很明显我不知道这么详细
Obviously, I didn't know those specifics,
但是我早知道你在骗人
but I knew you were lying.
Henry Coles不是我们要找的人
So Henry Coles wasn't the guy.
我的错
My bad.
还是有人在这条船上想杀我
There's still somebody on this boat who wants to kill me.
你想逍遥法外
You're trying to get away,
我不会让这发生的
and it's not gonna happen.
接下来的旅途我们要住在你的客舱里
We're spending the rest of this trip in your cabin.
Amy和我轮流值班
Amy and I will take sleep shifts
确保时刻有人盯着你
to make sure someone's always watching you.
谢谢 这让我觉得超级安全
Thank you. That makes me feel super safe.
如果你们想亲热
And if you want to smush,
我有眼罩和隔音耳机
I have a sleep mask and noise canceling headphones.
我们不能把他锁在里面吗
Can't we just lock him up in there?
我们真的要牺牲接下来六晚的睡眠吗
Do we really have to trade off sleep for the next six nights?
我知道 很抱歉
I know. I'm sorry.
但他说如果我们想亲热他会戴眼罩
But he did say that he'd wear a mask if we want to smush.
好吧 我明白了 他是庞蒂亚克大盗
Fine. I get it. He's the Pontiac Bandit.
你先开始轮班
You take the first shift.
谢谢你 你最好了
Thank you so much. You're the best.
嘿 纽约警局 放了他
Hey, NYPD! Let him go!
现在你相信我了吗
Now do you believe me?
那个人要杀我
That guy was trying to kill me.
好吧 有人想让你死
All right, fine! Someone wants you dead!
你赢了
You win.
亲亲 抱抱
Smush, smush
哦 我听起来还是像个天使
Ooh, I still sound like an angel.
你确定
You sure?
感谢上帝你当时在 Peralta
Thank God you were there, Peralta.
我知道你不会让最好的朋友死掉
I knew you wouldn't let your best friend die.
我还是要拘捕你 如果你死了我就不能了
I'm still gonna arrest you. I just can't do that if you're dead.
随便你怎么自欺欺人
Whatever you gotta tell yourself.
慢慢来 让他好好说话可真难
Baby steps. It's hard getting him out of his shell.
别提了
Tell me about it.
每次我们俩闹情绪 他就会说"尊棒 冲明"
Every time we get emotional, he's like, "Noice, smort."
我们能集中精神吗
Okay, can we focus up here?
我们还是不知道杀手长什么样子
We still don't know what your hitman looks like,
所以我们要把他"冲"出来
so we're gonna have to flush him out.
等一下
Wait a minute.
船上的厕所通到哪里
Where do the toilets on this boat go?
你不会想知道的
You don't want to know.
游泳池吗
The pool?
- 海里  - 更糟
- Ocean. - Oh, that's even worse.
我的虾就生活在海里
That's where my shrimp live.
总之 杀手可能会在今天下午
Anyways, he'll probably try to hit me
我表演的时候动手
at my show this afternoon.
至少我可以做着自己所爱的去死
At least I'll die doing what I love:
让大家在大海深处欲火中烧
getting people horny at sea.
真恶心
Yeah. Yeah. That's gross.
好吧计划是这样
All right, here's the plan.
我们要把你一个人留在舞台晃荡上作为诱饵
We're gonna leave you alone on stage and dangle you as bait.
该死 一个人晃荡当诱饵
Damn! Bait dangling?
如果我们和你一起在台上 可能会惊动他
If we're up on stage with you, it could spook him.
我们会混在人群里
We'll blend into the crowd,
我们会在他碰到你之前抓到他
and we'll take him down before he even gets to you.
我信任你
All right, I'll trust you.
但是如果你们要混在人群里
But if you're gonna blend in,
你们得融入
you got to blend in.
Rupert Holmes - Escape (The Pina Colada Song)
你们俩看起来不错
You two are looking good.
真的吗 我有点觉得我是
Really? I kind of feel
美国乡村摇滚男明星
Jimmy Buffett的网球教练
like I'm Jimmy Buffett's tennis coach.
不是的 很好看
No, it's working.
1980年播出犯罪题材电视剧
你知道我曾经超级迷恋<夏威夷神探>
You know I had a major crush on Magnum P.I.?
超级
Major.
哦 我应该留胡子吗
Oh, should I grow a moustache?
对 你应该留
Yeah, you should.
我不行 我身体不允许
Actually, I can't. I'm physically incapable.
我不应该提议这个 我们进去吧
I shouldn't have suggested that. Should we go in?
你找到我了
You found me.
在黑暗中喝苏打水
Drinking seltzer in the shadows.
我还是没法相信Debbie要和我共度六周
I still can't believe Debbie's gonna be staying with me for six weeks.
当你的邻居把很没品的音乐放超大声的时候
Sir, when your neighbor is playing their terrible music too loud,
你会让他们安静些吗
do you ask them to be quiet?
当然不啦
Hell no.
你要用你的垃圾淹死他们
You blast your garbage, and you drown 'em out.
你要以牙还牙啊
You got to fight drama with drama.
Debbie 这太过分了
Debbie, it's just too much.
- 发生什么了  - 我说你听着
- What happened? - Wait till you hear.
Kevin说 "嘿 我要去巴黎了"
Kevin is all, "Hey, man, I'm leaving for Paris,"
然后我说
And I said,
"那去好了 我不在乎"
"Then go already. I don't care,"
但是我在乎
But I do care,
现在我就是 "Kevin在哪"
and now I'm like, "Where's Kevin?"
我都不知道你们发生了这么多事
Well, I didn't know y'all had all of that going on.
没人理解我
Ugh, no one understands me.
现在你在这儿 我爱你
And now you're here, and I love you,
但是 我承受的太多了
but, like, it's a lot.
我生活中每件事现在都一团糟
Everything in my life is a hot mess right now.
该死
Damn.
警监 局长又打来了
Captain, the commissioner called again.
他想知道犯罪率什么时候下降
He wants to know when crime will be down.
你逗我吗 我该怎么和他说
Are you kidding me? What am I supposed to tell him?
我现在压力太大了
I'm under so much pressure.
我就是不能
I just can't even.
你身上的担子太重了
You got a lot on you.
如果这让你压力更大的话
And I don't want to overstay my welcome
我也不想打扰你太长时间
if that's gonna stress you out.
确实会 特别是在水星
It will, especially with Mercury in...
逆行的时候
retrograde.
抱歉
I am sorry.
我不知道 我来找你是因为
I-I didn't know. I mean, the only reason I came is...
Gary离开了我
'cause Gary left me.
什么
What?
他有了外遇
He was cheating on me.
但是 不 不 不 不
But you know what? No. No, no, no.
我不会再拿这个增添你的烦恼
I'm not gonna burden you with that, okay?
我会自己处理好的
I will deal with that myself.
越狱了
There's been a jailbreak,
又是黑帮干的
and the Mafia's at it again.
嘿 聊什么呢
Hey, what's going on here?
我都不知道我们还有这么多问题
I didn't realize we had more questions
要 一起 问Gotaro先生
to ask Mr. Gotaro together.
哦 没有 我一个人都问完了
Oh, we don't. I asked Mr. Gotaro all of them.
等等 Gotaro
Wait. Hold on. "Gotaro."
这是个安达卢西亚名字吧
Isn't that a Andalusian name?
- 是的  - 那真是巧了
- Yeah. - What a weird coincidence.
让一下Diaz警探
Pardon me, Detective Diaz.
昨晚我做了一大锅安达卢西亚小鳗鱼
Last night, I cooked up a ton of Andalusian baby eels.
别得寸进尺
Unbelievable.
我超爱鳗鱼
I love angula.
在这边很难买到的
I mean, it's impossible to find here.
哦 如果你像我一样收入不菲
Oh, not if you have a ton of disposable income
信用又好 那就不难了
and great credit, like I do.
你会喜欢的 我黄油(马屁)用(拍)得很到位
I think you're gonna love these. I really buttered them up.
哇 太谢谢了
Wow, thank you so much.
呃 走之前 我应该告诉你们
Uh, before I leave, um, I should tell you,
你们都是很棒的申请人
you're both great applicants,
但我已经把房子租给别人了
but I've decided to rent the apartment to someone else.
我对你的笑
I smiled at you.
都白笑了吗
For what?
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
鳏夫和寡妇们
widows and widowers,
欢迎来到全龄钢琴酒吧成人秀
welcome to the all-ages piano lounge adults only show.
我是Horatio Velveteen
I'm Horatio Velveteen.
- 名字带感  - 嗯
- Dope name. - Mm.
这是我写的一首小曲
This is a little song I wrote myself,
叫做"Rosa Rosa Rosa"
called "Rosa, Rosa, Rosa."
是这样唱的
Goes like this.
Rosa Rosa Rosa
Rosa, Rosa, Rosa,
- Rosa  - 这里人太多了
- Rosa, - It's so crowded in here,
而且灯光太迷离啥也看不清
and the lighting is way too sexy to see anything.
- 过来  - 好吧
- Come on. - Okay.
地板上站着的 就是你要找的人
Right there on the floor is the man you're looking for
他就在你面前 再往左一点
He's right in front of you. A little bit to the left.
我的左边 我的左边 我的左边 我的左边
My left, my left, my left, my left.
就这儿 穿红色衣服的那个
Come on this way he's in a red shirt.
不是那个亚洲老哥 我说的是亮红色
No, not the Asian dude. I'm talking about a bright red shirt.
那就是你要找的男人 那就是你要找的男人
That's the man you're looking for. That's the man you've been looking for.
- 我看见他了 跟我来  - 这仍然是一首爱的歌
- I got him. Follow me. - This is still a love song people.
诶我去
Ah, come on.
这仍然是一首爱的歌
This is still a love song.
跑哪去了
Where'd he go?
我的演出就此突然结束
Well, that ends my show, all of a sudden.
你们真是一群可爱的观众
You've been a great crowd.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
他要带我去你们亲热的地方
He's taking me where you smushed.
Jake 帮帮我 我还不想死
Jake, help me. I don't want to die.
我"权力的游戏"才看到第二季
I'm still on second season of "Game of Thrones."
把刀放下好吗
All right, just put the knife down, okay?
全龄钢琴酒吧里不能有谋杀
There's no murder in the all-ages piano lounge.
去你妈 死猪
Screw you, pig.
这句话太不老少咸宜了
That is not a very all-ages thing to say.
你真是完全没有进入这里的气氛
You just don't get the vibe here at all.
干得好 把那个绳子拿来
Nice, grab that cord.
把他绑起来 过来
Let's get his arms. Come here.
你被我女朋友"棍打"啦
You just got tanged by my girlfriend.
抱歉我知道听起来很恶心
Sorry, I know that sounded really gross,
但实际上是很赞的
but it was actually awesome.
你没事吧Judy
You okay, Judy?
Judy
Judy!
不 不不不不不
No. No, no, no, no, no.
再见Peralta 谢谢你救了我的命
Bye, Peralta. Thanks for saving my life.
不Judy 不要这样
No. Judy! Don't do this!
不 不要再耍我一次
No, not again!
Judy Judy
Judy! Judy!
Judy在哪 这船上所有地方我都找了
Where is Judy? I've looked everywhere.
他一定在这船上的某个地方
He has to be somewhere on this boat.
Peralta
Peralta!
不 他不在
No, he doesn't.
抱歉我这样对你 伙计
Sorry to do this to you, man.
我看见一个空档 不得不抓住了
I saw an opening, and I had to take it.
我不能进监狱 我太酷
I can't go to jail. I'm too cool.
我永远也不会放过你的 Judy
You'll never get away from me, Judy!
我听不见你在说什么
can't hear what you're saying.
你离我太远了
You're real far away.
我就假装你终于承认了
I'll just assume you're finally admitting
我们是最好的朋友
we're best friends.
不 我没有说那个
No, that is not what I'm saying!
谢谢你 这对我来说真的很重要
Thank you. It means a lot to me.
享受你的航海之旅把
Enjoy the rest of your cruise.
记住哦 你找到了一个好女人
Just remember, you got a fine lady.
不要强颜欢笑
Don't be a tang in the mud.
看看你的口袋
Check your pockets!
砰砰豪华舱 亲爱的
Boom-Boom Stateroom, baby!
太棒了
Awesome.
但我跟你还没完
But this isn't over!
我要追捕你到地球尽头
I will hunt you to the ends of the Earth!
我也爱你
I love you too!
能说出来我真的很骄傲
I'm so proud of us for being able to say it.
还站在那里干什么
What are you still standing there for?
- 去干柴烈火吧 - Judy
- Go smush! - Judy!
不
No!
好吧 但我的火车还有45分钟就开了
Well, okay, but my train is in 45 minutes.
没必要非得过来说再见吧
I don't have to say good-bye to Ray.
我不想给他压力
I don't want to stress him out.
不 他特意让我们叫你过来的
No, he specifically asked us to get you.
你好 Debbie
Hello, Debbie.
你搭了堡垒
You made a fort?
我想我们可以在这儿聊聊
I thought we could talk under here.
关于你和Gary的事儿
about you and Gary.
但
Well...
对不起 我想要把你赶走
I'm sorry I was pushing you away.
我想让你知道我一直在你身边
I want you to know that I'm here for you,
我非常愿意参与你的人生
and I would love to be all up in your life.
哦 你啊
Aw, you--
- 快给我个拥抱  - 好
- Give me a hug. - Okay.
好了
All right.
Gotaro先生
Mr. Gotaro.
你因涉嫌谋杀你的租户被逮捕了Shirley Crouch
You're under arrest for the murder of your tenant Shirley Crouch.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
是因为我没把房子租给你们吗
Is this because I didn't rent to you?
不是
No.
但这却很可疑
But that was suspicious.
为什么你不愿意租给信誉可靠的警察呢
Why wouldn't you want cops with great credit living in your building?
信用好还能买到鳗鱼
Great credit and an eel hookup.
因为你杀了她
Because you murdered her.
毒理学分析这位女士被投了毒
Toxicology report says the old lady was poisoned.
她的公寓有租金管制 你不能抬高租金
Her apartment was rent controlled, and you couldn't jack up the price
除非她搬走
until she was out of there.
我还有最后一个问题
I just have one last question.
如果你进监狱了 这里谁负责
If you go to jail, who makes the rental decisions in the building?
交给信托人
It'll pass to a trust.
由银行负责
The bank controls it.
游戏继续
Game back on?
如果你还用问 那你已经落后了
If you have to ask, you're already one step behind.
我还得把他带回警局
I should help bring him back in.
- 我们还是警察  - 没错
- We're still police officers. - Yeah.
嘿 能问你个事儿吗
Hey, can I ask you something?
嗯
- Mm-hmm.
如果这个厕所是冲到大海里的
If the toilets drain into the ocean,
那是不是小鲨鱼就能游上来咬我屁股呢
does that mean a tiny shark could swim up and bite me in the butt?
不 完全不能
No, not at all.
- 真无聊  - 这样吧
- Psh, lame. - Look.
我知道因为庞蒂亚克大盗的事情你很沮丧
I know you're bummed about the Pontiac Bandit
如果这算是安慰的话
so if it's any consolation,
我们可以剩下的时间
we could spend the rest of the cruise
都躺在床上吃大虾
eating shrimp in bed.
那简直是棒呆 但是不要
That is incredibly sweet, but no way.
我们要参加的活动太多了
We have too many activities to do.
你一定猜不到三分钟之后是什么活动吧
Eh? You'll never guess what starts in three minutes.
- 莎莎舞  - 哦 所以你能猜到
- Salsa dancing. - Oh, so you can guess.
谢谢你
Thank you for doing this.
我爱你
I love you.
尊棒 冲明
Noice. Smort.
我也爱你
I love you too.
而且 我非常肯定
Also, I think this is definitely
这是孤寡老人的舞蹈课
a dance class for widows.
- 不 我觉得不是  - 不是吗
- No, I don't think so. - No?
现在转向你的舞伴告诉对方你的伴侣是如何去世的
Now turn to your partner and tell them how your spouse died.
我觉得我们应该走了
Yeah, we should get out of here.
- 你确定吗  - 确定
- Are you sure? - Yes.
好吧
OK.
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组